<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CookEase</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">36774623226-c0dd5dphd14svvpnokn2loms4nmk8p5d.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="sample_instructions">Add salt to water and boil.\\nToast Quinoa for a couple of minutes in a dry pan  moving around so it doesnt burn (when you hear it pop, count to 5 and remove immediately)\\nAdd Quinoa and cook for 12 minutes on a soft boil, or until all the water is soaked into the Quinoa.\\nWhile cooking the Quinoa, add minced garlic to lemon juice, allow to sit.\\nRemove Quinoa from heat and add lemon juice and garlic mixture, mix well. Allow to absorb and cool.\\nChop all veg into similar sized pieces (I like about 1/4 dice).\\nChop parsley and mint finely.\\nWhen Quinoa has cooled, mix everything together. Serve with grilled shrimp!</string>
    <string name="sample_summary"><![CDATA[Quinoa Tabouli with Lemon Garlic Grilled Shrimp is a side dish that serves 4. One portion of this dish contains about \\u003Cb\\u003E14g of protein\\u003C/b\\u003E, \\u003Cb\\u003E3g of fat\\u003C/b\\u003E, and a total of \\u003Cb\\u003E248 calories\\u003C/b\\u003E. For \\u003Cb\\u003E$2.79 per serving\\u003C/b\\u003E, this recipe \\u003Cb\\u003Ecovers 28%\\u003C/b\\u003E of your daily requirements of vitamins and minerals. It is a good option if you\'re following a \\u003Cb\\u003Egluten free, dairy free, and pescatarian\\u003C/b\\u003E diet. This recipe is liked by 3 foodies and cooks. It can be enjoyed any time, but it is especially good for \\u003Cb\\u003EThe Fourth Of July\\u003C/b\\u003E. If you have quinoa, mint leaves, sea salt, and a few other ingredients on hand, you can make it. It is brought to you by Foodista. From preparation to the plate, this recipe takes about \\u003Cb\\u003E45 minutes\\u003C/b\\u003E. Taking all factors into account, this recipe \\u003Cb\\u003Eearns a spoonacular score of 82%\\u003C/b\\u003E, which is great. Similar recipes include \\u003Ca href=\\\"https://spoonacular.com/recipes/grilled-quail-with-pomegranate-orange-bbq-sauce-and-tabouli-with-quinoa-and-shredded-kale-286151\\\"\\u003EGrilled Quail with Pomegranate-Orange BBQ Sauce and Tabouli with Quinoan and Shredded Kale\\u003C/a\\u003E, \\u003Ca href=\\\"https://spoonacular.com/recipes/lemon-garlic-shrimp-with-quinoa-arugula-peas-556991\\\"\\u003ELemon Garlic Shrimp with Quinoa, Arugula & Peas\\u003C/a\\u003E, and \\u003Ca href=\\\"https://spoonacular.com/recipes/lemon-garlic-shrimp-with-radish-and-green-bean-quinoa-1422009\\\"\\u003ELemon-Garlic Shrimp with Radish and Green Bean Quinoa\\u003C/a\\u003E.]]></string>
</resources>